export const CourageQuizQuestions = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "What is the definition of courage?",
      options: ["Strength and bravery in the face of fear", "Physical fitness", "Intelligence", "Wisdom"],
      correctAnswer: "Strength and bravery in the face of fear"
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Who is the famous lion in 'The Wizard of Oz' known for his courage?",
      options: ["Leo", "Simba", "Aslan", "Cowardly Lion"],
      correctAnswer: "Cowardly Lion"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Which ancient philosopher said, 'Courage is the first of human qualities because it is the quality which guarantees the others'?",
      options: ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Socrates", "Confucius"],
      correctAnswer: "Aristotle"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "What is the term for facing physical danger for a cause one believes in?",
      options: ["Heroism", "Bravery", "Martyrdom", "Valor"],
      correctAnswer: "Heroism"
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "What is the famous quote about courage by Nelson Mandela?",
      options: ["'Courage is not the absence of fear, but the triumph over it.'", "'Courage is doing what you're afraid to do. There can be no courage unless you're scared.'", "'It takes a great deal of bravery to stand up to our enemies, but just as much to stand up to our friends.'", "'The greatest glory in living lies not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.'"],
      correctAnswer: "'Courage is not the absence of fear, but the triumph over it.'"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "What is the symbol of courage in many cultures?",
      options: ["Lion", "Eagle", "Sword", "Shield"],
      correctAnswer: "Lion"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "Which famous fictional character is known for his courage in the face of adversity?",
      options: ["Harry Potter", "Sherlock Holmes", "Frodo Baggins", "James Bond"],
      correctAnswer: "Harry Potter"
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "What is the title of a famous book about courage during the Holocaust by Corrie ten Boom?",
      options: ["The Diary of Anne Frank", "Night", "Schindler's List", "The Hiding Place"],
      correctAnswer: "The Hiding Place"
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "Who said, 'Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear - not absence of fear'?",
      options: ["Mark Twain", "Winston Churchill", "Martin Luther King Jr.", "Nelson Mandela"],
      correctAnswer: "Mark Twain"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "What is the term for courage that involves facing moral and ethical dilemmas?",
      options: ["Moral Courage", "Physical Courage", "Intellectual Courage", "Emotional Courage"],
      correctAnswer: "Moral Courage"
    }
  ];  